

Profile **Details** Croatia

I am a generative AI software developer with 5 years of experience in building projects, teaching coding, and automation. My expertise 00385992656398

and lies in developing full-stack applications and implementing generative Applicatic@gmail.com

machine learning technologies.

With prior 10 years of experience, I possess a comprehensive perspective on problem-solving and solution-finding. This is complemented by my effective business communication skills and project management experience, gained from leading and contributing to various projects...

Employment History

Software developer at techXflow d.o.o. (self-employed)

March 2024

• Software Development: Python, React, Flutter.

· Generative AI:

Large Language Models (LLM): ChatGPT

Gemini

Open-source models

Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG)

Al agents

• Cloud Computing: Google Cloud Platform.

Teacher & Head of Regional Compeatence Center at Technical School Čakovec, Čakovec

September 2018 — November 2023

- Led Comprehensive Lectures and Workshops: Covered subjects, including coding (Python, Flutter), automation, and business communication.
- Promoted a Culture of Experimentation: Fostered a learning environment that encouraged trying new things, practical application of theoretical knowledge, and viewing mistakes as essential learning steps.
- Played a prominent role in the implementation of two EU projects (EBRD - European Fund for Regional Development, ESF -European Social Fund) valued at €7.5 million
- Spearheaded multiple project-based initiatives

Previous Experience

June 2006 — July 2018

• Played key roles including Leadership in International Projects & Sales, Agency Director, Licensed Designer, Electrical Systems Designer, and Development Engineer, contributing to a broad range of projects.

Links

Personal Page Self-employed Page LinkedIn GitHub

Skills

Python

LLMs

RAG & Vectorbases

OpenAl API

REST APIs

Data Science & ML

Flutter

VS Code

Jupyter Notebook

Git/GitHub

GCP

Languages

Croatian

English

German

Hobbies

Reading: Technology & Future, People & Mindset, Personal Growth

Others: Running, Playing Guitar

Education

56 ECTS, Faculty of Organization and Informatics, Varaždin

2017 - 2018

- Specialization: Teachers Education (Pedagogical/Psychological/Didactic/Methodical)
- GPA: 4.55/5

University Specialist of Strategic Entrepreneurship, 60 ECTS, Faculty of Economics, Zagreb

2008 - 2011

- Thesis: Leadership in Social Responsibility & Social Entrepreneurship
- GPA: 4.6/5

Graduate Electrical Engineer (Industrial Electronics), 274 ECTS, Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Computing, Zagreb

2000 - 2005

- Thesis: Multichannel Receiver for Surface Electromyography
- GPA: 4.15/5

Natural Science and Mathematics Gymnasium, Čakovec

1996 — 2000

Awards: 1st (3x) & 3rd (3x) in County Mathematics Competitions (13-18 years)

Courses

Various online courses on topics: Python, LLMs, RAG, Vector Databases, Data Science, ML, Flutter, GCP and similar, - Udemy, DeepLearning.AI

2019 - 2024

Personal projects

2019 - 2024

- Educational Assistant App Study Buddy Frontend (Flutter), Backend (Flask)
- Machine learning manual based on Kaggles Titanik dataset
- Robotic arm system with Python GUI on Raspberry PI.
- ComfortClick-based home automation with integrated security and adaptive heating (KNX & Modbus).
- Raspberry PI web server for environmental data visualization.
- 3D printed foldable drone with betaflight.
- Personal and company webpage.